Get or set some values related to console screen window.

Window
Show the window title.

Window Size [width height]
Set window size in characters.
At end, previous window size is returned as width+(height<<16) in ERRORLEVEL.

Window GSize [MIN|MAX|REST|HIDE|SHOW]
Set window graphic size or show state.
At end, previous window client-area size in pixels is returned as width+(height<<16) in ERRORLEVEL.

Window GPos [x y]
Set window position in pixels.
At end, return previous window position in pixels as x+(y<<16) in ERRORLEVEL.

